本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
我们得给才艺表演想个节目
So we need an act for the talent show.
其实应该为高考复习复习吧
Or we could study for our s.A.T.S.
也该开始找找自己要报志愿的大学了
And start checking out colleges.
必须为未来做打算了
We do have our futures to think about.
节目要新颖点
Something fresh.
小伙子们 我们只是从这儿路过 不用在意
Hey, guys. We're just passing through, so don't mind us.
我特别想间你的 泰迪
Oh, I never mind seeing you, Teddy.
那我呢
What about me?
你么 我一点不想见
You I mind.
你们不介意让开地方吧
If you could move it along...
我们正在为才艺表演想节目呢
We're trying to work on our act for the talent show.
哎呀知道不 我是今年的主持人
Oh, you know, I'm the m.C. This year.
我希望你们错失冠军宝座可别哭哦
Well, I hope you don't mind second place,
因为我和斯宾塞要组成双人舞搭档呢
Because spencer and I are doing a dance act together.
你还和斯宾塞那小子瞎混啊
Still wasting your time with spencer?
他要不是空有其表 长的高点有有点脑子 谁知道会变成什么样的人呢
Take away his good looks, his height and his talent, and what have you got?
你这样的人
You.
好吧 我们该走了
I think we're done here.
兄弟 我一定要打败那个斯宾塞
Man, I would love to beat that spencer.
对 我们得想出好点子来
Yeah, we've got to come up with something good.
要绝佳的才艺表演
For the talent show, man.
我知道了
I got it.
我们可以表演传统把戏做腹语术
We go old school and do a ventriloquist act.
腹语表演是不是要带着一个会说话的木偶呀
Oh, a ventriloquist is a guy with a talking puppet, right?
对 就是傀儡
Right, a dummy.
嗯 不过有个小问题 我们有两个人
Oh, one small problem...there's two of us.
但是呢
Although.
我们俩其中一个人可以扮木偶
One of us could be the dummy.
-那就是你了-还是你吧
- Like you.- Or you.
-你去扮-还是你去
- Or you.- Or you...
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
就在这里  我们的家
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订： line WaitinZ
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
■
后期： Johnny-Z WaitinZ kenix
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十六集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E16  Duncan's Got Talent
阿乔 要是你打算取笑我的海报 我可不想听
Jo, if you're gonna make fun of my poster, I don't want to hear it.
我并没有打算取笑你那海报
I'm not gonna make fun of your poster.
我只想告诉你 你看上去蠢极了
I'm just gonna tell you it looks stupid.
你去投票给迪伦那小子好了
To ahead and vote for dylan.
我不想投给迪伦 他老挖耳屎
I can't vote for dylan. He's an ear-picker.
至少他没有继续挖鼻孔
At least he's given his nose a break.
盖比你要知道 你必须拉拢女选民们投票
You know, Gabe, you're gonna need the girl vote to win,
而你就好在遇上我 我可以帮你达成目标
Which, lucky for you, I can deliver.
-你又怎么可能做到-我们来制作一个竞选录像
- How would you do that?- We shoot a campaign video,
上传到班级主页上去公开播放
Post it on the class website.
对了 一定要拍到你家那个婴儿小妹妹
And we'll put your baby sister in it.
那些姑娘都可为宝宝着迷了
Girls go nuts over babies.
我不明白 不过女孩们就这样
I don't get it, but they do.
你为何想来帮我 我以为咱俩是敌对关系
Why do you want to help me? I thought we were enemies.
盖比 我们先不要给咱俩的关系下定义吧
Gabe, let's not put labels on our relationship.
咱俩心里都清楚那很复杂的
We both know it's complicated.
说正经的
No kidding.
我上个礼拜真的做了梦哎 梦见你
I had this dream last week where you...
哎呀 果然很复杂
Yeah, it's complicated.
看好 大概是这样的舞步
Okay, probably something like this.
明白了
Got it.
很好 那你现在做做
Cool.Now you do it.
没问题
Okay.
怎么样
So?
跳的很不错
Really good,
不过你没有照着我教你的舞步跳呀
But you're not doing what I showed you.
我晓得 但我觉得应该加多些变化 对吧
I know. I feel like it needs something more, right?
但是少了一点好
Or less.
其实我自己也有一些舞步 给你看下
Actually I've been working on some moves of my own, so...
我管这个动作叫做“打沙包”
I call this one "the hacky sack."
打呀 打呀
Hacky hacky.
打呀 打呀 打呀 打沙包
Hacky hacky hacky hacky hacky sack!
你觉得如何
What do you think?
你还想出些别的什么动作了吗
What else have you got?
那个
Well...
大家不是都知道有个爵士振手势动作吗
Everybody knows jazz hands, right?
是呀
Right.
让你见识下我的坏男孩舞
Check out these bad boys.
啪 啪 啪 啪 啪 啪
Pow pow pow pow pow pow pow pow!
啵
Pow!
爵士振动手的爆炸版
Exploding jazz hands.
难以置信呀
Fantastic.
现在我们先要拍摄展示你是一个强悍领袖的画面
All right, first we want to
show you as a strong leader.
显示你的强悍吧
So act strong.
这看上去怎么样
How does that look?
要我看什么啊
What am I looking at?
你只要捏紧拳头说“我为你们奋战”
Just make a fist and say,"I will fight for you."
行
Okay.
我将为你们奋战
I will fight for you!
完美 现在展示温柔一面的盖比吧
Perfect. Now let's see the softer side of Gabe...
一个有爱心的哥哥 追着宝宝四处爬的画面
The loving brother.Chase the kid around.
准备
Ready?
我要抓住你 抓到你了哦
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you.
哎呦 宝宝确实可爱极来了
Aww, the baby's absolutely adorable.
人们一定会爱死她的
People are gonna love her.
现在赶紧把她弄走吧
Now get her out of here.
那么现在让大家看看盖比的英明睿智
Now let's meet Gabe the wise leader.
好的
Okay.
我需要这样做吗
Should I do this?
不要
No.
-你只要回答以下的问题-好的
- Just answer these questions.- Okay.
盖比 你对学校放长假的提议怎么看
Gabe, how would you feel about a longer recess?
我认为此提议很好
I think it's a great idea.
有一部分老师则认为应该给我们布置更多的功课
Some of the teachers think we should have more homework.
你的想法呢
Thoughts?
我认为这种提议很糟
That's a terrible idea.
我们现有的功课量很合适
The amount of homework we do now is good.
那么最后对于新的操场规定 你是赞成还是反对
And finally, new playground rules... pro or con?
不支持也不反对 又要安全又要有乐趣
I don't like them at all.There's safety and there's fun.
是不可能两者兼顾的
You can't have them both.
说的很好 现在这样说
Loving it.Now say,
我是盖比 邓肯 证实此传递信息有效
"I'm Gabe Duncan and I approve this message."
I'm Gabe Duncan and I approve this message.
好极了 拍完啦
Awesome.We're done.
你要不要玩玩电动
You want to play a video game?
在选举之前
Until the election
我们最好保持纯专业的合作关系
I think it's best we keep this professional.
你应该去当木偶人
Or you could be the dummy.
是你应该去当木偶人
还是你才能胜任啊
Or you could be the dummy.
我们可以这样吵一整天啊
We could do this all day.
我们已经吵了一整天了
We have been doing this all day.
得了 我可不能当那个傀儡
Well, I can't be the dummy
因为我很怕你把手伸到我的衣服里面去那种感觉
'cause I'm not comfortable with you putting your hands up my shirt.
你上星期怎么没感觉啊
You didn't feel that way last week.
那时候自己够不到还尽叫我帮你挠痒痒
When you had that itch you couldn't reach.
好吧 我们俩一起当傀儡好了
All right, then what if we're both dummies?
很好 就一起当傀儡吧
Fine, we're both dummies.
我是不知道你们在搞什么
I don't know what's been going on in here,
不过你们俩终于有突破进展了
But you two just made a breakthrough.
喂 艾薇 你有空说几句吗
Hey, ivy, you got a minute?
你发现泰迪根本不会跳舞了 对吧
You found out Teddy can't dance, right?
她跳得太吓人了 我可不想在全校师生
She's awful.I don't want to embarrass myself.
面前丢脸 我该怎么办啊
In front of the whole school.What am I gonna do?
你必须直接告诉她
You gotta tell it to her straight.
干脆打开天窗说亮话就说
Just rip the bandage off and say,
姑娘 你太差劲了
"girl, you stink."
你知道 这种直言不讳的逆耳忠言
You know, that kind of honesty.
还是由闺蜜死党的嘴中说出比较好
Might be better coming from the best friend.
你真会开玩笑
You're funny.
好吧 去就去
Fine. I'll do it.
我会对她诚实以对的
I'll just be honest with her.
我扭伤了脚踝
I sprained my ankle.
哎呀天 怎么搞成这样
Oh, no. What happened?
我想练习一下你那种舞步来着
I was trying to practice some of your dance moves.
然后就滑到了
And then I slipped.
嗯 是不是做了太多打沙包的动作
Mm, too much hacking on the sacky?
对呀
Exactly.
正好在才艺表演开始前呢
And right before the talent show.
真是太不巧的时间了
Talk about bad timing.
你这可伶的家伙 快进来吧
You poor thing, come in.
快坐下
Have a seat.
来把你的脚搁在这儿
I'm gonna put your foot up.
你想吃点什么吗 是不是饿了
Can I get you anything? Are you hungry?
是有点饿
A little.
你知道自己应该吃什么吗
You know what you need?
要喝家里煲的鸡汤啊
Some homemade chicken soup.
哎哟 还要喝鸡汤咧
Mm, chicken soup.
给胆小鬼和正合适
For the chicken.
阿乔刚才上传了我的竞选录像到网上
Jo just put the campaign video on the website.
你们要不要看
You want to watch it?
很乐意啊 宝贝
Sure, honey.
大家对 盖比 邓肯了解多少呢
How well do you really know Gabe Duncan?
来跟我打啊
I will fight you!
他讨厌宝宝
He hates babies.
盖比 若是学校暂停放假你觉得如何
Gabe, how would you feel if there was no more recess?
我认为那很好
I think it's a great idea.
你说真的吗
Really?
那你怎么看减少作业量的观点
And what's your opinion about less homework?
那主意很糟
That's a terrible idea.
我们现有的功课量很合适
The amount of homework we do now is good.
最后请问 你怎么看女孩们呢
And finally, how do you feel about girls?
我一点都不喜欢她们
I don't like them at all.
盖比 邓肯
Gabe Duncan...
他不想要放假 想要给我们加功课量 还讨厌女孩子
No recess, more homework, hates girls,
特别讨厌女宝宝
Especially baby girls.
我是乔克依那 我希望做你们的班长
m jo keener and I want to be your president.
我是盖比 邓肯 证实此传递信息有效
I'm Gabe Duncan and I approve this message.
好吧 我知道这看起来不妙
Okay, I know it looks bad.
不过呢
But...
还不过啥呀
But what?
-好啊-嘿
- Hi.- Hi.
你一定是在想我怎么扭伤脚还能跑呢
You're probably wondering why I'm running on my sprained ankle.
没错 我确实很怀疑
Yeah, I kind of was.
因为伤已经养好了
It healed.
真的吗
Really?
那你为啥还拄着拐杖呢
Then why do you still have your crutches?
你真是好问不倦呀
Lots of good questions here.
斯宾思 到底怎么回事
Spence, what's going on?
好吧 说实话 我假装受伤的
All right, look, I faked the injury.
因为出了问题
Because there is a problem.
哪里出问题了
With what?
就是我们那个双人舞啊
With our dancing.
哎呀 斯宾思 不是每个人都能学会爆炸版的爵士手势的
Oh, spence, not everybody gets the exploding jazz hands.
一回生二回熟 要慢慢来
The first time out.It's a process.
不是我的问题
The problem wasn't me.
噢
Oh.
并不是什么大事 很多人都不擅长跳舞
It's no big deal.Lots of people can't dance.
你只是其中一个而已啦
And you're one of them.
我要更正你 我是个很棒的舞者
For your information, I'm a great dancer.
泰迪 我是想跟你说实话
Teddy, I'm just being honest.
你扭伤脚算是实话吗
Oh, like you were about your ankle?
哼 告诉你 我要跟你拆伙走别的舞搭子去
No, you know what? I'm gonna find myself a new partner...
我会找一个真正欣赏我才艺的人
- Someone who appreciates my talent.
泰迪别闹了
Teddy, come on.
我还特地给你织了可以保暖的脚趾袜呢
I even knitted you special socks to keep your toes warm,
这也是我另一个才艺 那就是给你这种人织毛衣
'cause that's another thing I'm good at... knitting.
我的班级在那边
My class is this way.
太好了 我们终于一致同意不玩腹语表演了
I'm so glad we decided to forget the ventriloquist act.
就是 我们俩之前太傻了 杂耍就简单很多
Yeah, what were we thinking? Juggling is so much easier.
好吧 那你先扔 -不 还是你先扔
- Okay, throw first.- No, you throw first.
-不 你先扔-不 还是你先扔
- No, you throw first.- No, you throw first.
埃米特 你要不要和我一起在才艺表演赛上跳舞呢
Emmett, do you want to dance with me in the talent show?
-愿意-很好
- Yes.- Great.
我们去地下室开始排练
Let's go to the basement and rehearse.
喂 喂 等等 埃米特 刚才发生了什么事
Whoa whoa, wait, emmett.What just happened here?
泰迪刚才叫我和她一起跳舞
Teddy just asked me to dance with her.
铁板钉钉了
Let's not question it.
那你就准备弃我而去啊
So you're just leaving me hanng?
别那样说嘛 你是我最好的哥们儿
Don't look at it that way. You and I are like best buds.
同甘共苦 风风雨雨都一起经历过来了
We've been through thick and thin together.
你知道我会一直陪伴你左右的
- You know I will always be there...
埃米特
Emmett!
回见啰
See ya.
啪 啪 啪 啪 啪
Pow pow pow pow pow!
啵
Pow!
你觉得怎么样 要说实话
What do you think? And be honest.
我很喜欢呀
I love it.Duh.
真的吗 因为斯宾塞说我跳得很差劲
Really? 'Cause spencer said I was a bad dancer.
我们不要再说斯宾塞那小子了
Let's not talk about spencer.
他是过去式 我埃米特才是现在时
He's in the past.It's emmett time.
那我们应该从我哪个舞步开始跳
So which of my moves should we start with?
其实我觉得我们应该把你的舞步保留到压轴
Actually I'm thinking that we should save your moves till the end.
好吃的甜点要最后上桌 对吧
You don't start a fine meal off with dessert, right?
说得对
Right.
所以让我先带头跳 你先跟着我就好
So I'll just start dancing,do whatever it is I do...
你知道的 先吃点肉啊土豆什么的
The meat and potatoes...
然后你就可以满载鲜花掌声 盛誉而归了
And then you can bring it home with the Crimble leg.
鲜花掌声的荣誉啊
The Crimble leg.
不过也要低调些
A little less Crimble leg
低调的荣誉啊
The Crimble leg.
再低调些
A little less.
还要低调嘛
Less?
对 再低点
More. Right.
-这样吗-对 就这样
- Crimble leg.- There you go.
嘿 今天选举怎么样啊 亲爱的
Hey, how did it go today, honey?
那个 有个小朋友说他投了我的票
Well, one kid said he'd vote for me.
后来他找到了眼镜才发现原来我不是阿乔
Then he found his glasses and realized I wasn't jo.
我们得教训一下这个叫乔的小孩
We have to do something about this jo person.
你没必要这样做
You don't have to do anything.
不行 我一定要去
No, I do, I do,
我可不准别人欺负我的小孩
Because nobody attack my babies.
现在老公 我要你去那个阿乔的家
Now bob, I want you to go over to jo's house.
把她老爸揍一顿
And punch her dad in the face.
要是他和那个阿乔是一个模子出来的 那我可不去
If he's anything like jo...no, thanks.
得 这回又是要靠老娘出马去踢馆了
Once again I am the one who has to do the butt-kicking around here.
亲爱的 你冷静点 没人需要去踢馆
Honey, would you relax? Nobody needs to kick anything.
说得对 我有个计划需要你们帮忙
That's right. I've got a plan and I need your help.
看见没 咱儿子自己有计划了
There, you see? He's got a plan.
对呀
Yes.
你就别在那压腿了 我们走吧
Would you stop stretching? Let's go.
我不是在压腿
I'm not stretching.
我是卡住不能动了
I'm stuck.
我看我们真的能胜哎
Hey, I think we can really take this thing.
看看这些对手都是啥垃圾啊 魔术师 滚轮溜冰的
Look who we're up against... the magician, the roller skaters,
踩高跷的 还有个吹大号的
The stilt walker, the kid with the tuba.
那个叫低音号 要不然就是像他戴着牙套发出的音节
It's a sousaphone or as he pronounces through his braces,
嘘嘘号
Shooshaphone.
刚才就是欧文带来的低音号
That was erwin and his sousaphone,
他的表演曲目是 随便你们信不信吧
Playing, believe it or not,
歌曲 美国派对
"party in the u.S.A."
（注：Miley Cyrus歌曲）
现在让我们欢迎舞蹈双人团体
And now please welcome the dance stylings of...
“移动力”组合
Locomotion!
埃米特
Emmett!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你离我远点
Get away from me.
谢谢 “移动力”组合
Thank you, locomotion...
和他们的朋友们
And friends.
现在是我们下一个节目
And now for our next act.
刚才还有人幸存吗
Did anyone survive that?
我还在呢
I'm still here.
请为腹语表演大师来些掌声吧
Please give it up for master ventriloquist.
P J 邓肯
P.J. Duncan!
大家好 我是PJ
Hi, everybody.I'm p.J.
她是查莉
This is Charlie.
问候大家吧 查莉
Say hello, Charlie.
我期待加可爱分的
I was hoping to get by on cuteness.
我们做的怎么样啊
How are we doing so far?
作为班长 我承诺代办你们的心声
And as your president I promise to represent you.
以我最大的能力为大家服务 我也承诺为你们战斗到底
I also promise to fight.
为了更多的假日和更少的功课的将来
For more recess and less homework.
最后一点 我当然不讨厌女孩子
And of course, I don't hate girls.
不像某些其他候选人
Like some candidates.
比如那个盖比 邓肯
Named Gabe Duncan.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
在我开始演说前 我想先谈谈这次竞选黑幕
Before I begin, I would like to say something about this campaign.
外界对我有很多流言
Now a lot of things have been said about me.
就算他们都是在中伤我 我也并不在乎
And even though they aren't true, I'm okay with that.
但是有人开始恶意攻击我的家人
But when somebody starts attacking my family...
这就触到我的底线
That's where I draw the line.
现在我要堂堂正正站在这里
Now I could stand here.
告诉你们一个真实的自己
And tell you who I really am,
不过我更愿意让你们亲眼看看
But I'd rather show you.
我爱我的每个子女
I love all my kids equally,
但如果非要选一个最得心的
But if I had to pick a favorite,
那就是盖比
It would be Gabe.
爸爸 我帮你的卡车换了机油
I changed the oil in your truck, dad.
不用多说甚么了 这就是好儿子盖比
Without being asked...classic Gabe.
他就是这么充满爱心喜欢照顾别人
He's just so loving and so caring,
特别是对他的小妹妹查莉
Especially with his baby sister Charlie.
事实上 盖比是对查莉的出生最热情的一个
In fact, Gabe was the most excited about Charlie's arrival.
他设置自己动手做了这个
And he made it himself.
盖比是那种你想跟他喝一杯的兄弟
Gabe's the kind of guy you want to have a root beer with.
(注：root beer是根汁汽水而不是酒)
必要的话我们可以再这儿熬一晚上
We'll stay up all night if we have to,
不过我还是要确保你能通过明天的考试
But I'm gonna make sure you pass that test.
你难道不需要去拯救那些流浪动物吗、
Don't you have to rescue stray animals.
为他们找到新家
And find them good homes?
在上学前已经做好了
Did that before school.
好兄弟盖比
Classic Gabe.
盖比不仅是又贴心又善良
Gabe's not only sweet and kind,
他还有特别棒的时尚触觉
He also has an amazing fashion sense.
这一件 有趣能逗乐
This one...fun and playful.
这一件嘛 潮爆了
This one is off the hook!
最后他们永远幸福的生活在一起
And they all lived happily ever after.
亲一个
Mwah.
盖比 邓肯
Gabe Duncan...
家庭永远第一位
Family first.
盖比 盖比 盖比 盖比
Gabe, Gabe, Gabe, Gabe!
-嘿-嘿
- Hey.- Hey.
我只是想跟你说
I just wanted to say...
我知道你想说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
你看了才艺表演现在想说“我早告诉过你”是吧
You saw the talent show and now you want to say "I told you so,"
因为你说的对 我确实不会跳舞
Because you were right.I can't dance.
其实我是想来道歉
Actually I was going to apologize.
因为我骗你说扭伤了脚
For lying about my ankle.
这样啊 那你继续
Oh, okay.Go ahead then.
很抱歉骗你说扭伤脚
I'm sorry for lying about my ankle.
我也很抱歉骗你说织了袜子
I'm sorry I lied about those socks.
什么
What?
其实不是我自己织的
I didn't actually knit them myself.
我根本不会织毛线 也不会跳舞
I can't knit.Or dance.
听着 要是我想找个会织毛线的舞蹈家
Hey, if I wanted a dancing knitter,
不然去跟贝蒂阿姨约会
I'd date my aunt betty.
那我们和好啦
So we're good?
特别好呢
We're great.
埃米特
Emmett...
离我远点
Get away from me!
嘿嘿 小查莉 昨天试学校的才艺表演日
Hey, Charlie. So yesterday was the school talent show.
我现在手里拿的是赢来的奖金25块钱的支票
And I hold in my hand the winning check for $25.
是PJ 邓肯赢来的
Which is made out to PJ Duncan.
对 因为用你的可爱分赢来的哟 小查莉
Yeah, the one that's based on your cuteness, Charlie.
还有我自己的可爱分
And mine.
不管怎么说吧 我自己却在学校欠了一大笔钱
Anyway, I on the other hand owe the school.
损坏公物的债务
Some money for damages.
还有欧文说他要“嘘”我上法庭
And erwin said he'll "shee" me in court.
所以我建议你
So my advice is,
以后要是有人跟你说你并不擅长某件你自己喜欢的事
If someone ever tells you you're bad at something you love,
千万不要放弃 但要再三保证
Don't give up.Just make sure.
绝对不要在全校面前去表演
You don't do it in front of the whole school.
还有要是我们什么时候打算教你跳舞的话
And if I ever offer to teach you how to dance,
那就祝你好运了 查莉
Well, good luck, Charlie.
盖比 吃中饭
Gabe, lunch.
场地安全
All clear.
盖比 你搞笑吧 这有没有必要啊
Gabe, really, is all this necessary?
绝对有必要 我现在是主席了
Yes, it is. I'm the president.
你只是十二班的主席啊
Of room 12.
今天是十二班
Today room 12,
明天就是十四班
Tomorrow room 14.
十二班粉刷教室 所以我们搬堂到十四班去了
They're painting room 12, so we're moving to room 14.
就吃你的三明治吧
Just eat your sandwich.
盖比 你这沾了点东西
Gabe, you got a little something on your...
哎呀 喂
Oh, whoa
盖比 能不能让你的特勤人员放开你的哥哥呢
Gabe, would you tell the secret service man to get off your brother?
妈妈 我说过不要再对我颐指气使
Mom, what did I say about bossing me around?
哦 你不会吧
Oh, you wouldn't.
给我拿下她
Take her down!
你有何要说的 爸爸
How are you doing, dad?
陛下圣明
I'm fine.